<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Guides on Lander</title>
    <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/categories/user-guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Guides on Lander</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/categories/user-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Customization</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/color-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/color-customization/</guid>
      <description>All colors of the theme can be customized through options in the site&amp;rsquo;s configuration.
The theme only requires the small version of Hugo as this is done through CSS variables, not Sass variables.
Options If an invalid option is supplied, it will not be rendered and a warning will be emmited.
Colors of a higher number are darker.
Primary Used mostly on buttons.
[params] [params.colors] primary-600 = &amp;#34;hsl(216, 40%, 32%)&amp;#34; primary-500 = &amp;#34;hsl(216, 45%, 35%)&amp;#34; primary-400 = &amp;#34;hsl(216, 55%, 40%)&amp;#34; Secondary Used on buttons, links and active TOC links.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Management</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/content/</guid>
      <description>For the best experience, content should be structured and configured according to this guide.
Sections All section list pages in the theme are rendered the same way. All section pages are rendered without pagination, sorted by category.
You can read more about customizing section list pages in the Section Customization with Front Matter guide.
Section Content Pages The front matter options available for section content pages are:
The title option used as the title of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start Guide</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>By the end of this guide you should have a Hugo site ready to be generated.
Quick Start Site The theme has a quickstart-site archive for every release. The archive contains a demo blog ready with the theme already set up inside.
Head over to the theme&amp;rsquo;s releases on Github and download the quickstart-site archive of the latest version.
After downloading, extract the quickstart site into an empty directory. The site should be ready for building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Section Customization with Front Matter</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/front-matter-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/front-matter-customization/</guid>
      <description>The root _index.md and section _index.md files render sections that are customizable through front matter options.
Section Options Some sections are only availbale for certain pages.
Most section options are optional, but it is recommended to fill all sections for optimal aesthetics.
Masthead The masthead section is available for both root and section _index.md files.
It is the background colored section with large titles right under the navigation. This is the element users usually see first and it can be used to guide them to important pages or download links.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>