<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guides on Lander</title>
    <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guides on Lander</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Customization</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/color-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/color-customization/</guid>
      <description>Lander only requires the non-extended version of Hugo to build. Every color in the theme can be customized without a Sass rebuild, thanks to CSS custom properties.
Lander is built around two types of sections: light and dark. Color customization is built around enabling independent coloring of each type. This means you can theme Lander with both section types dark, light or reversed.
Note all examples in this guide are in TOML.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Management</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/content/</guid>
      <description>For the best experience, content should be structured and configured according to this guide.
Sections All section list pages in the theme are rendered the same way. All section pages are rendered without pagination, sorted by category.
You can read more about customizing section list pages in the Section Customization with Front Matter guide.
Section Content Pages The front matter options available for section content pages are:
The title option used as the title of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development Guide</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/development/</guid>
      <description>Get familiarized with the development workflow of the project.
Installing Dependencies All dependencies in the project are managed through NPM, including Hugo.
To install the dependencies, open a command line at the root of the project and run:
$ npm ci To avoid package compatiblity issues, use Node version 12.x.
Hot Reload Servers Hot reload development servers can be launched for the demo site, the documentation or storybook.
Demo Run a development server of the demo site while watching the theme with Webpack:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start Guide</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>By the end of this guide you should have a Hugo site ready to be generated.
Quick Start Site The theme has a quickstart-site archive for every release. The archive contains a demo blog ready with the theme already set up inside.
Head over to the theme&amp;rsquo;s releases on Github and download the quickstart-site archive of the latest version.
After downloading, extract the quickstart site into an empty directory. The site should be ready for building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Section Customization with Front Matter</title>
      <link>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/front-matter-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lkummer.github.io/Lander/guide/front-matter-customization/</guid>
      <description>The root _index.md and section _index.md files render sections that are customizable through front matter options.
Section Options Some sections are only availbale for certain pages.
Most section options are optional, but it is recommended to fill all sections for optimal aesthetics.
Masthead The masthead section is available for both root and section _index.md files.
It is the background colored section with large titles right under the navigation. This is the element users usually see first and it can be used to guide them to important pages or download links.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>